LUIS ROGELIO ITURRA SARMIENTO

Digital and Multimedia Communicator
Universidad Tecnológica Metropolitana – UPA - MUT
+56975730425 – <u>iturra.roqelio@qmail.com</u> – https://rogepro.itch.io
https://www.linkedin.com/in/roqelioiturra/

Digital and Multimedia Communicator with 9 years of experience. Currently, he works as a QA Senior Software Specialist. He is an expert in software testing, project management, and is proficient in tools such as Unity, Git, and JIRA. He has contributed to projects for prominent clients like Banco Santander, Kongregate/Gamaga, and Claro-VTR ISP. Additionally, he leads quality control efforts and has impacted over 400,000 users across various platforms.

Professional experience

01.2024 - 03.2024 INTEGRATION PROJECT MANAGER / HAIBU SOLUTIONS

DEVOPS — E2E MANAGEMENT — ORACLE BUSINESS SUITE PRODUCT KNOWLEDGE — UNDERSTANDING AND STUDY OF CLIENT CLARO/VTR ARCHITECTURE — PROGRAMMERS TEAM MANAGEMENT — QUALITY CONTROL ASSURANCE — COORDINATION WITH DEVELOPMENT, ARCHITECTURE AND OPERATIONS DEPARTMENTS — 2.000 USERS.

10.2022 - 01.2024 QA BLOCKCHAIN TESTER - QA LEAD / KONGREGATE-GAMAGA

RESPONSIBLE FOR THE QUALITY AND CONTROL PROCESS – HARDWARE AND SOFTWARE TESTING – BUGS, ERROR AND IMPLEMENTATIONS REPORT – CASE MONITORING AND OPTIMIZATION IN WORKFLOWS – COORDINATION AND LEADERSHIP OF QUALITY AND CONTROL TEAMS – **70.000 USERS**.

12.2021 - 10.2022 QA TESTER / BYJUS-OCL PLAY

RESPONSIBLE FOR THE QUALITY AND CONTROL PROCESS – HARDWARE AND SOFTWARE TESTING – BUGS, ERROR AND IMPLEMENTATIONS REPORT – CASE MONITORING – **80.000 USERS.**

09.2018 - 12.2021 SYSTEMS ANALYST / NTT DATA - BANCO SANTANDER-SUPERDIGITAL

LIVEOPS – PROCESS TECHNICIAN – ITSCM – ANALYSIS OF BANK INFRASTRUCTURE SYSTEMS – ERROR SUPPORT IN TRANSACTIONS AND MONITORING - **250.000 USERS.**

01.2018 - 01.2019 2D ANIMATOR AND GRAPHICS DESIGNER / BADGE OF HEROES

ICONS DESIGN, ILLUSTRATIONS EMOJIS FOR CAFÉ JUAN VALDEZ CLIENT – GAMIFICATION PROCESSES – ICONS ANIMATION – UI/UX DESIGN.

01.2018 - 01.2019 HARDWARE DEVELOPTMENT / DIEZCUANTRO.

HARDWARE AND SOFTWARE PROTOTYPING PROCESS FOR DOMINGO HARDWARE SOLUTIONS — DEVELOPMENT END TO END DIGITAL FLOWMETER WITH DASHBOARD SUPPORT — IMPLEMENTATION OF ARDUINO TECHNOLOGY, MOTHERBOARD DESIGN, SOLAR PANELS AND DATA VERIFICATION.

01.2015 - 01.2017 MULTIMEDIA PRODUCER / MINDBENDER DYNAMICS

EARTH CATEGORY WINNER IN THE SPACE APSS CHALLANGE 2015 – START-UP CHILE GENERATION 14 WINNER – LINKO APP DEVELOPMENT TO DETECT VECTORS DISEASE IN CROPS –GRAPHIC PIECES, UI/UX AND MULTIMEDIA PRODUCTS DEVELOPMENT.

06.2015 - 12.2015 PRODUCTION ASSISTANT/ BENEROT

INTERSHIP – VIDEOGAME PRODUCTION ASSISTANT – GDD DEVELOPMENT FOR STATE TRADE FUNDS.

01.2015 - 06.2015 PRODUCER / CIMMERIAN GAMES

GAME BOARDS DEVELOPMENT AND PRODUCTION – GROWTH HACKING – SHOW RUNNER IN MAGIC SUR GAME BOARD GATHERING 2015

Education

2016 - 2020

Digital and Multimedia Communication with a mention in 2D/3D Animation and New Media Technology - UNIVERSIDAD TECNOLÓGICA METROPOLITANA – UPA.

2018 - 2018

International Exchange scholarship, Entrepreneurship & Strategy – **TORONTO METROPOLITAN UNIVERSITY, CANADÁ.**

2013 - 2014

Level Technician in Digital Animation and Video Game Design **UNIVERSIDAD DEL PACÍFICO.**

2013 - 2014

Construction Engineering

UNIVERSIDAD ANDRÉS BELLO.

Knowledge Tools/Frameworks

English – B2 Autodesk Suite
Microsoft Office 365 Adobe Creative Suite

Android Blender Windows UNITY MAC UNRFAL Linux Github WebService JIRA **Procesos Batch** SOAPUI SQL Postman HTML Selenium **CSS** Slack

C# Google Suite
Javascript AWS
Python ID@XBOX

Lua

Recomendations

Craig Reeve – QA Manager Gamaga – 56976107335 – cr33v3@gmail.com

Julian Liberona – Risk Manager Banco Estado – 56984286778 – irliberona@gmail.com

Felipe Rebolledo – Strategy Integration VTR – 56963751507 – felipe.rebolledo@clarovtr.cl